kwiklearning.com 2013-06-09

# Kwik Learning - Speed Reading, Memory & Brain Performance Training Privacy Policy

Effective Date: January 1, 2011

PLEASE READ. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS SUBJECT TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY AND THE WEBSITE [TERMS AND CONDITIONS](http://superheroyou.com/terms-conditions/).

Index

I. Notice  
II. Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect  
III. E-mail Newsletter Subscriptions  
IV. User Accounts  
V. Special Promotions and Purchases; Submission of Content to be Published  
VI. Information Collected by Other Means or Media  
VII. Information About Other People  
VIII. Customer Service  
IX. Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect  
X. Cookies and Related Technology  
XI. Special Notice Regarding Children Under 13  
XII. Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information  
a. Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
b. Personally Identifiable Information  
XIII. Our Commitment to Data Security  
XIV. Hyperlinks To and From Other Sites  
XV. Consent to Processing in the United States  
XVI. Contact Us Regarding Privacy  
XVII. Notification of Changes

## I. Notice

The Website refers to the website at [www.SuperheroYou.com](http://www.superheroyou.com/) and [www.KwikLearning.com](http://www.kwiklearning.com/) as well as any of its sub-domains and related domains. This Website is owned or operated by Kwik Learning, LLC. and/or its subsidiary companies in the United States of America (collectively, “COMPANY”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to information that you provide to COMPANY via this Website, and/or by use of other services (collectively, the “Services”) that may be provided by other means or media, including as set forth below and as defined in the applicable [Terms and Conditions](http://superheroyou.com/terms-conditions/) or other terms.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you notice of COMPANY’s information management practices, including the types of information gathered, how it is used and safeguarded, and the degree to which you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information. Your use of any COMPANY Service or Website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms. This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated by reference into the [Terms and Conditions](http://superheroyou.com/terms-conditions/) for this Website.

## II. Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect

COMPANY respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personally identifiable information that you provide in connection with your use of its Websites and Services.

## III. E-mail Newsletter Subscriptions

To subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, if any, you will need to provide your e-mail address. You may also be asked for other information when you subscribe.

## IV. User Accounts

In order to use our chat rooms, message boards, and certain other Services, you will need to register and create a user account (“User Account”). There is no cost to create a User Account in most cases. You may be asked to choose a user name, screen name, or member name (each, a “User Name”) and password. Please do not use your real name or the real name of another person when selecting a User Name. You will also be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information and other information about yourself, such as your first and last name, date of birth, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.

Please note that your User Name will be available to the Internet’s general public while you participate in some Services, like chat rooms, forums or message boards, so you should exercise discretion when using these Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in such Services. In some instances, you may choose to create a “Public Profile” that will be available to others on the Internet. Public Profiles are managed entirely by you, and you are solely responsible for your Public Profile’s content and its “public” or “private” status. The Company bears no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information that users may disclose in user forums or other public areas of this Website. You are also responsible for maintaining and updating the registration information in your User Account with current and complete information. You may access, edit or remove your Public Profile by signing in to your User Account and following the directions there. You can also send an e-mail to [support@kwiklearning.com](mailto:support@kwiklearning.com) to request deactivation of your User Account.

Please review our restrictions on use and guidelines for user forums in the “Terms and Conditions” for the Website.

You can unsubscribe from receiving commercial e-mail from the Website by clicking the link contained within such e-mails sent to you. You should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our databases. In addition, we may institute a policy in which user information is deleted after a certain amount of time, and therefore, your user information may no longer exist in the COMPANY’s active database(s). In addition, even if you choose to unsubscribe or otherwise modify your User Account settings, the COMPANY reserves the right to contact you regarding your account and your use of this Website.

## V. Special Promotions and Purchases; Submission of Content to be Published

To participate in some Services such as sweepstakes, contests and surveys (“Special Promotions”), or to make online purchases (“Purchases”), you will need to provide personally identifiable information, such as name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, and date of birth. Your information may be collected by COMPANY or by a third party, such as a co-sponsor or a vendor involved in, or providing services in connection with, a Special Promotion, or an e-commerce partner in the case of a Purchase.

If you make a Purchase or enter a sweepstakes or other Special Promotion on one of our sites or through our Services, COMPANY will collect your personally identifiable information, and you are deemed to consent to us providing your information to third parties who provide certain services such as processing of credit card transactions, customer service, promotion or sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable. (As more fully described below in “Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Information – Personally Identifiable Information”, these third parties are prohibited from using this information for their own marketing purposes and/or from sharing, selling, or otherwise distributing any personal data of our customers, unless you choose to opt in for such additional uses and/or disclosure by the third parties, under their respective privacy policies.). Also, by entering a sweepstakes or other Special Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that sweepstakes or other Special Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion.

If you make a purchase or enter a promotion (such as a sweepstakes) in which COMPANY is participating on a third party’s website (or through some other means or medium), we will collect your information from the third party only if you opt-in to receive additional communications from us, or we are required to fulfill some function in relation to your activity (e.g., to send your order or deliver a prize).

If you submit to the Website a comment, photograph or other content to be published, online or offline (including on-air, in a DVD, or any other format), we may publish your name or other personally identifiable information in connection with publishing the content and you are hereby deemed to give us permission to do such.

## VI. Information Collected by Other Means or Media

In some situations, we may also collect personally identifiable information and other information about you through other means, directly or indirectly. For example, if you access any COMPANY content, or purchase such content via your wireless carrier or through another third party, the COMPANY may collect information directly from you or through the third party. Likewise, if you use our software, or provide information to other companies who share information about their customers, we may collect additional information about you. In each of these cases, the COMPANY will apply this policy to any personally identifiable information.

## VII. Information About Other People

Some COMPANY Websites and Services may ask you to submit personally identifiable information about other people. If you provide us with personally identifiable information of a friend, or your friend provides personally identifiable information about you, to e-mail a feature from the Website, the e-mail addresses you or your friend supply us for those activities will not be used to send you or your friend other e-mail communications unless disclosed at the time you provide the information. A record of that transaction will be maintained as allowed and/or required by law.

## VIII. Customer Service

Some Services may offer support and technical assistance through customer service centers via telephone, online chat, or e-mail. Whenever you communicate with customer service, you do so with the understanding that an operator may view and make changes to the information in your User Account in order to provide the assistance that you need.

## IX. Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect

As part of the registration process for some Services, you may be asked to provide information that does not personally identify you. For example, you may be asked to provide information concerning your personal preferences, purchasing habits, and the like. This information is generally optional but may be included in your User Account profile. COMPANY requests this information to understand you better and to also bring to your attention new services, programs, or offers that may be of interest to you.

In many cases, COMPANY will automatically collect certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of its sites and Services. COMPANY might collect, among other things, information concerning the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your “click path” through the COMPANY sites or “click-through” from an e-mail, the Website or advertisement that was linked to or from the COMPANY site when you visited, and your IP address. To do this, COMPANY may use cookies and other technology (see below). If you are using our wireless Services, we may also automatically collect information such as the type of wireless device you are using, your mobile identification number (assigned by your telecommunications carrier) and telecommunications carrier. Your use of our Websites and Services, and information provided through these technologies, will be anonymous unless you provide us with personally identifiable information or have provided such information in the past.

## X. Cookies and Related Technology

This Website’s pages or e-mail messages may contain cookies, web beacons (also known as clear gifs), or similar technologies as they become available. Cookies are information files that this Website may place on your computer to provide extended functionality. The COMPANY may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as tracking usage patterns on the Website, measuring the effectiveness of advertising, limiting multiple responses and registrations, facilitating your ability to navigate the Website and as part of a verification or screening process. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You should refer to your browser instructions, “Help” screen, or similar such resource to learn more about how to manage cookies and possibly reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent by indicating this in the preferences, options, or similar such menu in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of this Website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies and you may not be able to take advantage of some of this Website’s features. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

The COMPANY’s web pages may include advertisements for third parties and their products, and those third-party advertisements may include a cookie or web beacon served by the third party. The COMPANY does not control cookies in such third party ads, and visitors are encouraged to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. The COMPANY’s Privacy Policy does not cover the use of information collected from you by third party ad servers. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

A web beacon is a small graphic image that allows the party that set the web beacon to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of the web page, web-based document or e-mail message, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. Web beacons can be very small and invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page or e-mail, including HTML based content, can act as a web beacon. The COMPANY may use web beacons to count visitors to the web pages on the Website or to monitor how our users navigate the Website, and the COMPANY may include web beacons in e-mail messages in order to count how many messages sent were actually opened, acted upon or forwarded.
